https://softubcanada.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Softub
Language
[glt language="English" label="English"]
[glt language="French" label="Francais"]
Dealers
Want to be a Dealer?
Careers
Why Softub?
800-668-8827 (TUBS)
Build Your Tub
Softub 140 (1-2 people)
Softub 220 (3-4 people) Softub 300 (5-6 people)
×
No products in the cart.
Home / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Softub Canada’s Privacy Policy
Softub Canada is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of contact information you share with us (the phrase “contact information” means any information by which you can be contacted, such as your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you what contact information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review, correct and opt out of our use of, the information. This policy applies to customers in Canada and other markets served by Softub Canada.
As a part of our commitment to your privacy, Softub Canada supports and adheres to the retail industry’s common guidelines and practices concerning digital marketing. We will (1) provide customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information rental, sale or exchange with other marketers; (2) honour customers’ requests not to share their information with other marketers; and (3) honor customers’ requests not to receive mail, telephone or other solicitations from Softub Canada.
COLLECTING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU
There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product, subscribe to a service, or to participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions, etc.) when we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, etc. We may also maintain a record of your product purchases.
Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our web site. In addition, we may need to contact you via phone, email or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you have opted to not receive communications from us.
USING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU
We use the contact information you provide for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration, analyzing preferences, trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers, and providing you with information from and about Softub Canada. From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our Select Partners. In such cases, we might rent, exchange, share and/or cross-reference information, including contact information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.
To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, in our stores or through our catalogs. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our Select Partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize the shopping experience of you and others with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.
We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data management, promotional services, etc. We call them our Service Providers. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We also ask our Service Providers to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours.
Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your contact information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to Softub Canada or to others. We may also disclose your contact information when we believe the law or legal process requires it.
EDITING, UPDATING, CORRECTING AND DELETING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive direct marketing from us, or if you would like to opt out of our rental or exchange of your information with other marketers, please let us know by sending us an email. Please be sure to include your full name, email address, mailing address, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing address or other contact information with us please contact us the same way.
Please note that any requests to remove or update your contact information may take up to ten days for your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request.
PROTECTING CHILDREN
Softub Canada takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. Our web sites are general audience sites. We do not permit anyone under the age of 13 to register with us. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13.
Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any contact information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children’s online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children’s access to the web.
COOKIES
Our web sites use “cookies.” We may also use cookies in emails that you receive from us. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products, services and advertising to suit the personal interests of you and others, estimate our audience size, assist our online merchants to track visits to and sales at our sites and to process your order, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or analyze your visiting patterns.
Certain of our Service Providers may use cookies and collect information on our behalf. They are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our other Service Providers. However, we respect your right to choose whether to be included in such services. You may opt out of certain of these services at any time. In addition, in connection with the services that they provide to us, certain of our Service Providers may work with third parties who may use cookies to collect anonymous information to tailor advertising for you and others elsewhere on the web. These third parties do not have access to any contact information about you. If you would like to opt out of accepting cookies altogether, you can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. However, certain features of the web site or our services may not work if you delete or disable cookies.
SECURITY
We take precautions, including use of sophisticated encryption and authentication tools, to protect the security of your contact information that you share with us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your contact information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web sites, and you do so at your own risk.
We urge you to keep your password and other sensitive information in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also, remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.
POLICY CHANGES
If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our web site. Those changes will go into effect on the effective date posted in the notice and at the end of the revised Privacy Policy. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our web site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. Your continued use of our web site or services constitutes your consent to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
YOUR FEEDBACK
To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. You may email us or call us at sales@softubcanada.com or 800-668-8827.
Who We Are
Softub Canada has been distributing and manufacturing the Softub in Canada since 1990. Softub is Canada’s truly portable hot tub, weighing as little as 50lbs empty.
READ MORE
Site Map
Covers
Surrounds
Accessories
Videos
Career Opportunities
Dealers
FAQs
Testimonials
Contact Us
About Us
Connect With Us
Corporate Headquarters: 967 Falconbridge Road, Sudbury,
ON Canada P3A 5K8
800-668-8827 (TUBS)
info&commatsoftubcanada&periodcom
Newsletter
Sign up to our monthly newsletter to stay up to date with the most recent news, events and promotions.
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Refunds and Returns
Methods of Payment
© 2020 Softub Canada | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy | Refunds and Returns | Powered by Web Conductors
We accept:
×
Your next big purchase just became more affordable! Softub Canada has partnered with FinanceIt to offer you a flexible monthly payment plan for your purchase. Find out if you’re approved in seconds – no obligation, no commitment.
APPLY NOW
×
Your next big purchase just became more affordable! Softub Canada has partnered with FinanceIt to offer you a flexible monthly payment plan for your purchase. Find out if you’re approved in seconds – no obligation, no commitment. APPLY NOW
×
Join Softub
Username
Email
Sign up
Login to Softub
Username
Password
Login Lost Password?
Reset Password
Enter the username or e-mail you used in your profile. A password reset link will be sent to you by email.
Username or E-mail
Get new password
Loading...
Don't have an account? Sign Up
Already have an account? Login
Notice
Shipping dates may vary depending on shipping company delays and other factors. Please be patient and we will get your order to you ASAP
×
X
